<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Teraku&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://teraku.de/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Teraku&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 10:24:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://teraku.de/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>📚 Review: Mythos Geldknappheit</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/mythos-geldknappheit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 10:24:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/mythos-geldknappheit/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This blog post will be in German, as the book I am talking about is also in German
 Für wen ist dieses Buch? Ich habe heute das Buch &amp;ldquo;Mythos Geldknappheit&amp;rdquo; von Maurice Höfgen fertig gelesen. Vorab kann ich schon einmal sagen, dass ich das Buch allen wärmstens ans Herz lege, die
 einen tieferen Einblick in die Gewerke der MMT haben möchten, die MMT mit einem leichten Europa Touch verstehen möchten, oder für ihre progressiven Gesellschaftsentwürfe einen makroökonomischen Unterbau suchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intention in languages</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/intention-in-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 20:18:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/intention-in-language/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I think about what a bliss computers are. I don&amp;rsquo;t mean in a way of how they have improved our quality of life (which they did) and I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to disregard of the fact that they have had and will continue to have lots of implications on our social interactions and sociatal perception. What I mean is the fact that we now have these machines which obey exactly the way as we tell them to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prices of german houses</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/house-prices-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:46:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/house-prices-2020/</guid>
      <description>Prices of german houses So for a while I had a scraper running, which, once a day, scraped housing prices from chosen regions in Germany. I accumulated about 6 month of data until I stopped it, mainly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I&amp;rsquo;d ever properly utilise it.
I decided to at least show some of it. This post is basically excerpts from a Jupyter notebook. A link to the data can be found at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting my RSS reader to my blog&#39;s webring</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/blog-setup-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 11:36:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/blog-setup-deployment/</guid>
      <description>Outline Since I am using openring, I will detail how I automatically update the posts in the webring for this blog with the feeds from the blogs I follow.
My RSS feed / news-flash Finding the stored feed data I&amp;rsquo;m using the RSS reader news-flash. So the first order of business was finding out where where and how my feed was stored. Since news-flash is FOSS, a quick into the sourcecode revealed the following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing a workflow graph</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/workflow-graph-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 09:06:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/workflow-graph-implementation/</guid>
      <description>Goal Implement a struct which holds the workflow graph and yields the next values in line for execution.
Workflow Graph When writing a workflow management engine, one has to decide on the data structure of the workflow. I decided to go for the most common one: A directed acyclic graph, in short DAG. I thought about using a more open type, i. e. a cyclic graph, but that has really weird implications for a retry system and output handling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
