<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Teraku&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://teraku.de/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Teraku&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 20:18:23 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://teraku.de/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intention in languages</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/intention-in-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 20:18:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/intention-in-language/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I think about what a bliss computers are. I don&amp;rsquo;t mean in a way of how they have improved our quality of life (which they did) and I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to disregard of the fact that they have had and will continue to have lots of implications on our social interactions and sociatal perception. What I mean is the fact that we now have these machines which obey exactly the way as we tell them to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prices of german houses</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/house-prices-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 17:46:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/house-prices-2020/</guid>
      <description>Prices of german houses So for a while I had a scraper running, which, once a day, scraped housing prices from chosen regions in Germany. I accumulated about 6 month of data until I stopped it, mainly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I&amp;rsquo;d ever properly utilise it.
I decided to at least show some of it. This post is basically excerpts from a Jupyter notebook. A link to the data can be found at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting my RSS reader to my blog&#39;s webring</title>
      <link>https://teraku.de/posts/blog-setup-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 11:36:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraku.de/posts/blog-setup-deployment/</guid>
      <description>Outline Since I am using openring, I will detail how I automatically update the posts in the webring for this blog with the feeds from the blogs I follow.
My RSS feed / news-flash Finding the stored feed data I&amp;rsquo;m using the RSS reader news-flash. So the first order of business was finding out where where and how my feed was stored. Since news-flash is FOSS, a quick into the sourcecode revealed the following.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
